#### Contact

vjmitt33@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/veronicabonaby-3b212266 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Microsoft Office Customer Service Microsoft Excel

# Veronica Bonaby

Travel RN at Maxim Health Care

Atlanta, Georgia

## Summary

I have been a Registered Nurse for 14 years. My choice to become a nurse was one of which that has not changed since I was a little girl. However, parenting 4 daughters has really taken front and center of all I do today. Nonetheless, I am happy and proud to face the world everyday knowing that I have compass these two challenges, but not yet! I am still reaching farther, higher and stronger. "V"

## Experience

Maxim Health Care Travel RN June 2016 - Present (4 years 1 month) Varies

Anthem

Case Management

August 2013 - May 2016 (2 years 10 months)

**Utilization Management & Case Management** 

### Education

Walden University

Master of Science in Nursing Leadership and Management · (2011 - 2013)

Mercer University